Speaker today, mr
今天的演讲者，先生
Shi, investor relations
史，投资者关系
associate director of the area
区域副主任
Please go ahead, sir
先生，请先走一步。
Thank you
谢谢
Hello, everyone
大家好，大家好
Welcome to our first 1/4
欢迎来到我们的第一个四分之一
2021 earnings call
2021年财报电话会议
Joining us today
今天加入我们
our founder and CEO of tuya, miscarry wang
我们途亚的创始人兼首席执行官王流利
and our CFO, mr
和我们的首席财务官，先生
Jesse lil
杰西·李
You can refresh our first quarter of 2021
您可以更新我们2021年第一季度的
Natural results
自然结果
are our conflict investor relations website
我们的冲突投资者关系网站
at hayato to yahoocom
从早藤到Yahoocom
You can also access a replay of this course
您还可以访问本课程的重播
where it becomes available in a few hours
几个小时后就可以买到了
Our IR website, before we start with
我们的IR网站，在我们开始之前
know that this core
我知道这个核心
may contain forward-looking statements made
可能包含前瞻性陈述
presents to the safe harbor provision for
向安全港条款提交
the private securities litigation reform act
私人证券诉讼改革法
of 1995
1995年号
These forward-looking statements
这些前瞻性陈述
are based on measurements, current expectations
都是基于测量结果，当前的期望值
and observations
和观察
that involve known and unknown risks
涉及已知和未知风险
and uncertainties and other factors
以及不确定因素和其他因素
not under the communist control
不在共产主义控制之下
which may cause actual results, owen
可能会导致实际结果，欧文
or achievements of the company
或公司的业绩
to be materially different from the results
与结果大相径庭
performance or expectation inside
内部绩效或期望值
already looking statements
已在查看的报表
All looking for statements expressly qualified
所有人都在寻找明确限定的语句
in their entirety by the cautionary statement
全部由警告性声明
Risk factors
风险因素
binding with testing
绑定与测试
the basal circumference
底围
Hope I will now turn the porch
希望我现在能把门廊
Always present, because today, folder and see
永远存在，因为今天，文件夹和查看
of twitter's necessary wall is another three
推特必备的墙中还有另外三个
other something in see
请参阅中的其他内容
150 can take away a hundred
150个可以带走100个
We had to wait and to come to the thesis
我们不得不等待，然后才能谈到论文。
you don't lie
你不会撒谎的
So saying, christian counseling
这么说吧，基督教咨询
and gentile people union d 2 minus 1
和非犹太人联盟d 2减1
So competent am andre
我很能干，安德烈
I'm back
我回来了
I told you that I would get a TA
我告诉过你我会请助教的
or council 3w eclipses
或议会3w日食
You turn that these aren't we, are you
你转过身来，这不是我们吗，是吗？
So to you that someone will tell you that
所以对你来说，有人会告诉你
be done coaching
做完辅导了吗？
You don't just show you the penis
你不能只给你看阴茎
Can use almond tissue called italian food
可以用杏仁纸巾做意大利菜
Kinkaku-ji
金卡库吉(Kinkaku-ji)
The survey
这项调查
Hello, everyone
大家好，大家好
I am the founder and CEO of to
我是TO的创始人兼首席执行官
Yeah, but it is one charity
是啊，但这是一家慈善机构
and thank you for joining us
感谢你们收看我们的节目
on our first learning school
关于我们的第一所学习型学校
as a public company
作为一家上市公司
We're very pleased to report a two hundred
我们非常高兴地报告200个
two hundred thousand
二十万
year over year growth in our single revenues
我们的单项收入同比增长
achieving US dollars
实现美元
Fifty point
50点
nine million for the first quarter of 2021
2021年第一季度为900万
Revenues for our primary iot passes
我们主要物联网通行证的收入
and our staffs business
和我们的员工业务
both achieve over 220 percent
两者都达到了220%以上
year-over-year growth
同比增长
Your very able
你非常能干
We're very happy
我们非常高兴
that we were able to accomplish all of this
我们能够完成这一切
more, continuing to improve our gross margin
更重要的是，继续提高我们的毛利率
which increased by ten point
增加了10个百分点
eight percentage points year-over-year
同比提高8个百分点
to 411%
至411%
Such robust results
如此强劲的结果
were driven by three main factors
是由三个主要因素驱动的
First, we capitalize on strong
首先，我们利用强大的
global demand for iot products and services
全球对物联网产品和服务的需求
Second
第二
we cultivated sustainable growth in demand
我们培育了可持续增长的需求。
from our partners by empowering them
从我们的合作伙伴那里获得支持
with our innovators
与我们的创新者一起
and scalable cloud platform
可扩展的云平台
to become leading iot companies
成为领先的物联网公司
in their respective industries
在各自的行业中
First
第一
we attracted a large number of new customers
我们吸引了大量的新客户。
from various industries and buildings
来自各行各业和建筑物
of range of industry verticals reserve
行业垂直储量范围
by leveraging our reputable brand equity
通过利用我们享有盛誉的品牌资产
and the network effects of our cheery
以及我们欢呼的网络效应
our ecosystem
我们的生态系统
male
男性
The price of the property you can
你所能买到的房产的价格
How can you, kinky
你怎么能这样，怪胎
We're not killing and eating a pay on time
我们不会按时杀戮和吃饭
Good evening
晚上好
to gene that we are indians
我们是印第安人的基因
under either
在以下任一项下
Change your hypothesis, face and for you
改变你的假设，改变你的面子，为了你
two to the k factor
2到k的因子
sudan 2013 in the earthly one
人间的苏丹2013
to crisis center center, one to go
去危机中心，还有一条路要走
tony died on the sunday supplement
托尼在“星期日”增刊上去世。
ping time
Ping时间
putting us soon and as you can see by
就像你看到的那样，很快就会把我们放在一边
into tee major
转成发球台大调
So iíd say you turn into union
所以我会说你变成了工会
calling us to ensure
打电话给我们以确保
out to start to the morning, susan, can you
苏珊，明天早上出发好吗？
Surgeon, toyota and honda 10 cannot be met
外科医生，丰田和本田10号不能满足
First, I'll go into greater detail
首先，我将更详细地介绍一下
about the demanded country
关于被要求的国家
During the quarter, more than 39
在本季度，超过39
million smart devices were deployed
部署了100万台智能设备
with iot path services
使用物联网路径服务
showing a strong growth of demand for it
显示出对它的需求的强劲增长
products
产品
During the quarter
在本季度内
the global economy rebounded
全球经济回升
as covid vaccine coverage improved
随着Covid疫苗覆盖率的提高
in major economic regions around the world
在世界主要经济区域
Over the last year
在过去的一年里
forced closures and quarantines
强制关闭和隔离
Have until
一直到
new habits of using small devices at home
在家中使用小型设备的新习惯
This lets you
这使您可以
rapid increase in the number of registers
寄存器数量迅速增加
smart device developers on our platform
我们平台上的智能设备开发人员
from approximately 260000
从大约260000
at the end of last year
在去年年底
so more than 320000
所以超过320000
at the end of the first quarter
在第一季度末
So the more contact with services
因此，与服务的接触越多
are becoming
正在成为
the new standards for many transactions
许多交易的新标准
In the post covid economy, for example
例如，在后舒适经济中
the demand for continuous check in at hotels
酒店对连续入住的需求
has grown rapidly
发展迅速
This shift in user habit
这种用户习惯的转变
is becoming increasingly prominent in the spend
在消费方面变得越来越突出
a madeira and changing the way people work
马德拉酒和改变人们的工作方式
study and a chain themselves
书房和链条本身
According to see, I see the worldwide iot path
根据SEE，我看到了全球物联网路径
total addressable market
总目标市场
is forecasted to grow
预计将会增长
at a caterer of 189%to 171
在189%到171%的宴席承办人
110 the 17 billion US dollars by 2024
110到2024年170亿美元
In addition, based on idc's for cos
此外，基于CoS的IDC
Theta, the worldwide iot software
Theta，全球物联网软件
total addressable market
总目标市场
is forecasted to grow at a kegger of 129%
预计将以129%的速度增长
to 237 billion us dollars by 2024
到2024年达到2370亿美元
Thank the audience to react to trinity
感谢观众对三位一体的反应
and I think our culture
我认为我们的文化
to do you enhance this one
要增强这个吗？
the local community
当地社区
the bay hold up
海湾挺住了
and do the unions
工会要做的就是
that we have to turn the heat down to the out
我们必须把暖气调低到室外
He passed
他通过了
They won't
他们不会的
The kohu
科胡岛
2003 I mean, I got a couple grand kahuna
2003年，我的意思是，我有几个大卡哈纳
go EGT the am an asshole
去吧，我是个混蛋
Ooh, this is quite a weekend
噢，这可是个不错的周末
And the same time to teach you things
同时教你一些东西
I need, of course
当然，我需要
conducted a training camp in connecticut
在康涅狄格州举办训练营
This is sweet
这太甜蜜了
So once he did, I scare you
所以一旦他这么做了，我就吓到你了
Powerful guy training program by logan, UT to
德克萨斯州洛根推出的实力派培训计划
do you mean-
你的意思是-
students who call themselves the timing
自称时机的学生
pane they herself to the to team was won
他们自己到了TO队就赢了
Ton, ton
吨，吨
She'll totally under control, thank you
她会完全控制住的，谢谢
since you were a young poof away
从你还是个年轻的浪子开始
couch until tender
把沙发放在沙发上，直到变软
Next, I'll discuss the sustainable growth
接下来，我将讨论可持续增长
to launch
下水
we have cultivated from existing customers
我们是从现有客户那里培养出来的
by delivering the best value possible
通过提供可能的最佳价值
through our innovative
通过我们的创新
highly scalable cloud platform
高度可扩展的云平台
We mabel customers to grow into iot leaders
我们向客户推荐成长为物联网领导者
in their respective industries
在各自的行业中
As a result, their demand for our services grow
因此，他们对我们服务的需求不断增长
as they expand
随着他们的扩张
the number of products they develop
他们开发的产品数量
on our platform
在我们的平台上
Our double bass
我们的低音提琴
man expansion rate for iot past
物联网过去的城域网扩展率
with and 10 presents
带和10份礼物
for the trailing 12 months
在过去的12个月里
ended march 31st, 2021
截止到2021年3月31日
We have now surpassed the industry average
我们现在已经超过了行业平均水平。
for the sixth consecutive quarter
连续第六个季度
since we began tracking the metric
自从我们开始追踪这个指标
We were also able to achieve this primarily
我们也能够初步实现这一点
We were able to achieve this
我们能够做到这一点
primarily because of
主要是因为
the quality and scope of our women's golf
我国女子高尔夫球的质量和范围
iot past products
物联网过去的产品
which deliver tremendous value to our customers
为我们的客户带来巨大价值
On the cloud platform
在云平台上
our customers can develop competitive
我们的客户可以开发好胜
and cost-effective products
和高性价比的产品
with very little RD , investment
只需很少的研发投资
We also enable customers
我们还使客户能够
to expand into new product categories
拓展到新的产品类别
and geographic regions on our platform, which
以及我们平台上的地理区域，
With hundreds
数以百计的人
and hundreds of thousands of products
数十万种产品
can use in over 200 countries and regions
可在200多个国家和地区使用
around the world
在世界各地
our platform enables customers to
我们的平台使客户能够
upgrade their business models
升级他们的业务模式
from a traditional sales oriented business
从传统的以销售为导向的业务
to a service-oriented iot business
面向服务的物联网业务
Nana, who died
娜娜，她死了
a large number of customers on the tree
树上有大量的顾客
a cloud platform has developed into a wire
云平台已经发展成为一条电线
to leaders in their respective industries
致各自行业的领军人物
As of march 31st, 2021
截至2021年3月31日
the number of premium customers
高级客户的数量
who contributed over 100000
他贡献了超过100000
US dollars in revenue during the trailing
往绩期间的美元收入
12 month period grew to 1216
12个月期限增长至1216个月
from 188 as of december 31st, 2020
从截至2020年12月31日的188人
During the first quarter of twenty
在20年前的第一季度
Twenty-One in one of our brand
21合1我们的品牌
customers plays
客户实演
more than five times the number of orders
订单数量的五倍多
from the same period last year
与去年同期相比
Thank you, sally
谢谢你，萨莉
We are useful to you
我们对你很有用
That's our sewing
那是我们的缝纫
Thank you, don
谢谢你，唐
quoting his own that do you think
引用他自己的话，你认为
I don't know
我不知道
I meant to shoot what I am
我的意思是拍摄我现在的样子
clint, a couple yards of it and call you reach
克林特，几码后打给你
We are not on our feet and go
我们不是站着走的
do you got in the nappy later
你晚些时候上尿布了吗？
Once, yoni honking-how you doing
有一次，约尼按喇叭-你好吗？
She couldn't do the simple things
她不会做简单的事情
And korea next week
和下周的韩国
More color on how we love recent
更多关于我们是如何喜欢最近的
about the effects of archaea ecosystem
浅谈古细菌生态系统的作用
and a grant application
以及拨款申请
to acquire new customers
争取新客户
from different industries
来自不同行业的人
it is general consensus for iot grants
这是物联网拨款的普遍共识
that end users
最终用户
need to have the ability to control multiple
需要能够控制多个
smart devices with one single application
具有单一应用程序的智能设备
Therefore, being able to
因此，能够
connect with thousands of other brands
连接数以千计的其他品牌
on the tree, our cloud platform
在树上，我们的云平台
brings tremendous value to our customers
为我们的客户带来巨大价值
This network effect
这种网络效应
a lot of synergy between our partners
我们的合作伙伴之间有很大的协同效应
and also create
还可以创建
create significant barriers to entry
设置巨大的进入门槛
from our competitors
从我们的竞争对手中脱颖而出
The more brantley half of our platform
我们平台的布兰特利越多
the more new brands want to join our forum
希望加入我们论坛的新品牌越多
Thanking in DC to warm the house here
感谢华盛顿让这里的房子暖和起来
path goes to liam from wheaton, done in pencil
从惠顿到利亚姆的小路，用铅笔画的
he values his own house
他看重自己的房子
He the past in turn, could
他反过来在过去，可以
How will you buy food
你将如何购买食物？
And don't you try asking the nothing
难道你不试着什么都不问吗
I could do it in from 320 by
我可以从320到
Got something that tension over you
在你身上有一种紧张的感觉
like me to do that
像我这样做的人
could handle your kohu countdown
我可以处理你的Kohu倒计时
woman the entire time
从头到尾都是女人
Yeah, more than corfu
是啊，比科孚还多
Thank you, troy
谢谢你，特洛伊
Key commands
关键命令
samsung on auto tagging is all cute
三星在自动贴标签上都很可爱
Home actually occur
家实际上发生了
He's a fake hope in time
他在时间上是一个虚假的希望
the old so deal that got him in time
使他及时赶到的那笔旧交易
I need to intro to find some world
我需要介绍一下才能找到一些世界
won't have him locked up
不会把他关起来
You guys famous to chain one girl
你们这些家伙因为用链子锁住一个女孩而出名
What do you think
你怎么认为
Who got going it, daniel suit
谁开始行动了，丹尼尔·西装？
I stand out hunting daughter king
我在猎杀女儿王时脱颖而出
Later time him
以后再找他
since he met in the into the altitude whole
因为他是在进入高空的整个过程中相遇的
we pull up
我们把车停下来
and are developing their product on
并且正在开发他们的产品
Some of these cost include, dental gammage
其中一些费用包括，牙科伽玛术
multinational
多国
air conditioning and energy solutions provider
空调和能源解决方案提供商
more than half of well-known german
超过一半的知名德国人
pioneer in heating and ventilation technology
采暖和通风技术的先驱
Art slick, one of the largest
艺术浮雕，最大的艺术浮雕之一
Why good producers in europe
为什么欧洲的好制片人
with over 50 percent of market share in turkey
在土耳其拥有超过50%的市场份额
and its sovereign beckel
以及它的君主贝克尔
being the second largest brand in europe
成为欧洲第二大品牌
Lock in luck
锁定运气
a world-renowned household kitchen
世界知名的家庭厨房
where brand in south korea
韩国的哪个品牌
I hope
我希望
a healthier and beauty in the tronics
电子竞技中更健康、更美丽的人
Manufacturers
制造商
with product in tens of millions of homes
产品遍布千家万户
and millions of hotel rooms in north america
以及北美数以百万计的酒店客房
Am smith
Am Smith
and american water heating and water treatment
和美国的水加热和水处理
for his provider
对于他的提供者来说
with a multi-billion dollar market cap
拥有数十亿美元的市值
and one engine state of 147 years has history
一台发动机长达147年的状态已经有了历史
Jesco and american home electronic company
杰斯科与美国家电公司
with 3500 products
拥有3500种产品
sold in 85 thousand stores
在8万5千家商店销售
across north and south america
横跨南北美洲
Stick leading electronic blends in the zoo
Stick是动物园里领先的电子混合产品
offering over 50 types of electronics
提供50多种电子产品
with industrial, commercial
有工业的，商业的
and residential use cases
和住宅使用案例
Wiper and indian it giant
雨刷和印度it巨头
with 40 billion us dollars market cap
市值400亿美元
real me opens houses, smart device
Real Me开房，智能设备
Brent was only group
布伦特是唯一的团体
the largest security door company
最大的防盗门公司
cool company and many more
很酷的公司，还有更多
We couldn't do the good through that hole
我们不能通过那个洞做好事
until she down or putting you in some sense
直到她把你打倒或者从某种意义上说
that we are healthy
我们是健康的
Pass-and I'm not changing medicine
通过-我不会换药的
survey, period
调查，期间
You need to be under the influence of
你需要受到
an adult area immediately
立即进入成人区域
I mean, some telecom payouts
我是说，一些电信支出
Learning social power
学习型社会力量
the voted on the male authors
投票选出了男作家
Goons to tell
打手们要告诉我们
See some prototype
请看一些原型
the opium pipe powered by two young
由两个年轻人提供动力的鸦片烟斗
certain PBT
某些PBT
follow peru leaders and also 317
跟随秘鲁领导人，也是317
Societal payment issue
社会支付问题
Chance to it under the in societal testing
在社会测试中获得它的机会
age to 18
年龄至18岁
Gender transition
性别转型
See, opium pipe survey
看，鸦片烟斗勘测
powered by three and thirteen years to do
由三年和十三年的时间提供动力
high solution, which will call
高解决方案，它将调用
Meanwhile, we're seeing more regional details
与此同时，我们看到了更多的地区性细节
from the leaders, including telecom operators
来自领导，包括电信运营商
to three a coyote pass services
提供三个郊狼通行证服务
to empower their private brand smart devices
支持他们的自有品牌智能设备
This includes companies such as a rajaiah
这包括像Rajaiah这样的公司
the largest indonesia retail chain
印尼最大的零售连锁店
store telecom
商店电信
the largest telecommunication operator
最大的电信运营商
in indonesia
在印度尼西亚
Tower, well, a well-known more
塔台，嗯，知名的更多
they can reach our channel
他们可以到达我们的频道
Tell, the largest mail order company in germany
Tell，德国最大的邮购公司
and many more, in fact'is private labels
事实上，更多的是“自有品牌”
from more than 40 leading retail companies
来自40多家领先的零售公司
in europe were all powered by chuya
在欧洲都是由丘雅提供动力的
Or, as we like to say, PBT little
或者，正如我们喜欢说的，PBT很少
the largest food retail company in europe
欧洲最大的食品零售公司
is one such company during the quarter
是一家这样的公司在本季度
Several top retail companies
几家顶级零售公司
in north america have also chosen to be
在北美也选择了
in the fourth quarter of this year
在今年第四季度
Can I hold you down
我能按住你吗？
G20
20国集团(G20)
hi, elliot of peru
嗨，秘鲁的埃利奥特
Young condom condom for me, too
我也要年轻的避孕套
He did a deacon counter
他做了一个执事计数器
I'm confirming to the kohanim
我正在向科哈尼姆确认
attending saint paul, minnesota, and do see you
参加明尼苏达州的圣保罗，一定要见到你
See you choose
看你选吧
Our company
我们公司
typically controlled and owned a cumbia
通常控制和拥有一只小黄牛
Later in the timing chains and I have
在稍后的计时链中，我有
item will add
项目将添加
the seed of woman who see the kombu
看到昆布的女人的种子
In addition to acquiring new customers
除了获得新客户之外
we also expanded our services
我们还扩大了我们的服务范围。
to include an entirely new product categories
包括一个全新的产品类别
leverage
杠杆作用
Leveraging the scalability of our platform
利用我们平台的可扩展性
we glue
我们粘合在一起
the number of rescues supported by our iot
我们的物联网支持的救援数量
path segments
路径段
to 210000 by the end of the first quarter
到第一季度末降至210000
from 250000 at the end of last year
从去年年底的250000
During the first quarter
在第一季度
we expended in too many new
我们花了太多的钱买新的
PDG product lines
PDG产品线
Many international brands in a yemm's
许多国际品牌在Yemm‘s
have entered into trial or mass production
已进入试验或批量生产
of products
产品的数量
such as personal transport developers
例如个人交通开发商
including unicycles and scooters
包括独轮车和滑板车
With any new shipments in the tens of millions
如果有数以千万计的新出货量
digital appliances
数字家电
including fast charging devices
包括快速充电设备
and gaming like strips, with any achievements
和游戏就像条带一样，有任何成就
in the hundreds of millions
在数亿美元中
smart wearables, including watch bracelet
智能可穿戴设备，包括手表手镯
And where is any shipments in the billions
数十亿美元的出货量在哪里？
Sports and health products
体育保健品
including jump wrote dumbbells
包括跳跃写的哑铃
badminton racket
羽毛球拍
rowing machines and truck moves, etc
划船机和卡车搬运等
Etc, industrial and commercial gateways
等，工商门户
and finally, lighting products
最后，照明产品
such as highway lights and landscapes
例如高速公路灯和景观
Nights in the first quarter
第一季度的晚上
we also develop a series of low power
我们还开发了一系列低功耗
security products, such as low power doorbell
安防产品，如低功耗门铃
camera locks and more
相机锁等
This is also a category
这也是一个类别
with very strong and consistent demand
有着非常强劲和稳定的需求
Above all, we also developing int
最重要的是，我们还开发了int
pass products for new energy
为新能源传递产品
industrial and agricultural vehicles
工农业车辆
will share more details, then one
会分享更多细节，然后
Regarding this
对此，
new verticals in coming quarters
未来几个季度的新垂直市场
These are convinced a woman
这些都使一个女人确信
I would constitute an engine
我会组成一个引擎
And so we are into special
所以我们进入了特别的
I am what I am
我就是我自己
so you click
所以你点击
you can get house has passed a couple to
你可以让豪斯已经过了几次
our hard-working
我们辛勤的工作
kinda in general is coming to answer
大体上来说，我的回答是
The three primary factors
三个主要因素
were the main growth drivers for our LT
是我们LT的主要增长动力
plus segment
加细分市场
Next, I will share some updates on our
接下来，我将分享一些关于我们的
star fragment
星形碎片
We started to launch services
我们开始推出服务
at the end of 2019
2019年底
and the current service
和当前的服务
stages of development
发展阶段
and when continue to make great strides
当我们继续大踏步前进的时候
to improve and launch more stuff products
改进和推出更多可补充的产品
in this segment
在此细分市场中
Our biggest competitive advantage
我们最大的好胜优势
is the fact that our to your cloud platform
事实是，我们向您的云平台
has hundreds of thousands of global
拥有数十万的全球
iot developers
物联网开发者
Our platform is neutral and open
我们的政纲是中立和开放的。
platforms that can provide our case
可以提供我们案例的平台
our customers
我们的客户
with a varied selection of multi branded
有多种选择的多品牌
hardware choices
硬件选择
Thank you, though
不过，还是要谢谢你
Do i, during the first quarter, sorry
在第一季度，我是不是很抱歉
during the first quarter
在第一季度
we were actively working on version 10
我们正在积极开发版本10
size upgrade for our smart
针对我们的SMART产品进行尺寸升级
community and real estate services
社区和房地产服务
to integrate multi-terminal
要集成多个端子，请执行以下操作
interactive entrances to just a little bit
互动入口只有一点
Over a year
一年多来
we have joined the upper echelon of china
我们已跻身中国的高层行列。
smart community and real estate asset
智能社区和房地产资产
as writers
作为作家
We have now served in
我们现在已经在
many of china's leading real estate groups
中国许多领先的房地产集团
including bank of group, santa ocean group
包括Bank of Group，Santa Ocean Group
chat, overseas lime and investment
聊天、海外石灰和投资
kaiser group, citron, quantitative element
凯撒基团，香茅，定量元素
billion international holdings and sunday
十亿国际持有量和周日
So this group apologies with china
所以这群人对中国表示歉意。
overseas land investment and kaiser prosper
海外土地投资与凯撒繁荣
Both began in the first quarter of this year
这两家公司都是在今年第一季度开始的。
So if you didn't call me back
所以如果你不给我回电话
we also release a premium version of our
我们还发布了我们的高级版本
smart hotel and apartments a
智能酒店和公寓a
solutions in the first quarter of this year
今年第一季度的解决方案
The premium version expands all services
高级版扩展了所有服务
from simple hotel room management
从简单的酒店客房管理
to encompass hotel
包罗万象的酒店
lobby and facility traffic management
大堂和设施交通管理
New version also supports energy management
新版本还支持能源管理
a key focal points for most hotel managers
大多数酒店经理的主要关注点
She asked smart hotel and apartments a solution
她向智能酒店和公寓咨询了一个解决方案。
already powers 25000 booms in china
已经为中国的25000个围栏提供动力
Now, with the endemic proving around the world
现在，随着世界各地的地方病证明
we have begun to enter overseas markets
我们已经开始进军海外市场。
I'm assuming you mean once
我猜你是说一次
and thanks to father who died to me, de luca
多亏了为我而死的父亲，德卢卡
exactly
一点儿没错
I'm hyundai
我是现代
You get started
你可以开始了
You can go that when a while
你可以在一段时间后再去
Peter, I'm convinced
彼得，我确信
we also announced version 20
我们还宣布了版本20
for our smart consumer security SAS
针对我们的智能消费者安全SA
in the first quarter
在第一季度
upgrading the beckham into smart security
将贝克汉姆升级为智能安全
service platform
服务平台
Customers can manage multiple households
客户可以管理多个家庭
or commercial devices through a unified
或商用设备
unified portal
统一门户
By creating a closed loop
通过创建一个闭环
data connection between home devices
家庭设备之间的数据连接
and commercially managed security services
和商业管理的安全服务
we're able to realize the standardized
我们能够实现标准化的
business interface
业务接口
with third-party security operators globally
与全球第三方安全运营商合作
Our smart consumer security south
我们南区的智能消费者安全系统
has already received orders
已经收到了订单
from a number of security operators in china
来自中国的多家安全运营商
and vertices, including golden lock safety
和顶点，包括金锁安全
the largest store security operator in china
中国最大的商店保安运营商
That's okay, dad
没关系，爸爸
Sometimes two
有时两个人
three
三
that than contiguity people, typically
比起邻里相亲的人，通常
and thousands and thousands of tourists
成千上万的游客
enter them
输入它们
in the to tell me tommy
告诉我汤米
tommy john elliott, mmm
汤米·约翰·埃利奥特，嗯
He took up in high seattle supercenter
他在西雅图高级购物中心工作。
cuckoo three central cooperative
杜鹃三中心合作社
I also sang and candida
我还唱了一首歌，唱了一首
she's gonna see santa
她要去见圣诞老人
Smart the measure, lighting fast was launched
聪明的措施，闪电快推出
in the second quarter of last year
在去年第二季度
and the first quarter of 2021
2021年第一季度
We launched version 10 of our smart
我们推出了我们的SMART 10版本
commercial lighting SAS
商用照明SAS
which is functions in smart construction
这就是智能建筑中的功能
remote monitoring and you can function
远程监控，您可以
monitoring operations and maintenance
监控操作和维护
And more smart commercializing SAS will
更聪明的SA商业化将
promote the enhancement of commercial lighting
促进商业照明的增强
business models, creating
业务模式，创建
an unforgettable customer experience
难忘的客户体验
and substantial energy savings
以及大量的能源节约
For example, excerpts, groups
例如，摘录、组
three-story flagship store in shin-chan
位于新昌的三层楼高的旗舰店
use our commercial lighting SAS
使用我们的商业照明SAS
to create a uniquely autistic
创建一个独一无二的自闭症患者
shopping experience
购物体验
Some gas stations have saved more than
一些加油站已经节省了超过
thirty percent in energy usage with our
30%的能源使用率与我们的
smart commercial lighting fast
智能商业照明快速
dozens of china's leading marketing companies
数十家中国领先的营销公司
including NBC lighting
包括NBC照明
skyblast lighting and trillions
天爆照明和数万亿美元
the old customers of tuya
途雅的老客户
smart commercial lighting fast
智能商业照明快速
The segment also has many customers
这个细分市场也有很多客户。
such as system operators in europe
例如欧洲系统运营商
hong kong and more
香港及更多
I'm not used to that learning
我不习惯那样的学习
Junior johnson, please
小约翰逊，请给我
Here you go, woman, do you
给你，女人，你要吗？
A search with a fact that you can call
带有事实的搜索，您可以调用
somebody from sterling
一个来自斯特林的人
early in the fire seemed to teach the hood home
大火的早期似乎教会了兜帽人回家
So, yeah, I can see that
所以，是的，我看得出来
The article as well
这篇文章也是如此
starting an early age in terms of design
在设计方面从小就开始了
sheet assassin hose
刺客床单软管
Well, what we can see is at all-time
嗯，我们能看到的是在任何时候
most at the time, camping place in good health
大多数时候，露营的地方身体都很好
Can see since the buddha
可以看到自佛以来
English and sources such as business
英语和商务等资源
is also showing early signs of high
也出现了早期的高吸收率的迹象
repurchase rapids
回购急流
following its launch in may 29
在五月二十九日推出后
In our hotels, hospice
在我们酒店，临终关怀
has welcomed its first group of contract
已经欢迎了它的第一批合同
renewals with a renewal rate of over 90%
续约率超过90%的续费
Thank you, group
谢谢你们，小组成员
I'll first birthday, SAS customer
我要过一岁生日了，SAS的客户
So one
所以只有一个
of the largest real estate groups in china
中国最大的房地产集团之一
signed a second phase SAS
签署第二阶段SAS
contract with us at the beginning of this year
今年初与我们签约
Sunday service group, our first
周日服务小组，我们的第一个
smart communities as customer
智能社区即客户
and a top 100 real estate gripping
最吸引人的100个房地产排行榜
branagh has signed a threat faced
布拉纳已经签署了一份面临的威胁
a set of contract with us in february this year
今年2月与我们签订的一套合同
This contract follows their first ways
这份合同遵循了他们的第一条道路。
contracting august 20, 20
签约8月20日，20日
and second face contract in october 2012
和2012年10月的第二份Face合同
Auntie, going forward
阿姨，往前走
we'll continue to polish our staff
我们将继续完善我们的员工
products and events al graduate
毕业后的产品和活动
entry of various a services into global market
各种a服务进入全球市场
That whole look
整个造型
anytime we like to meet, I see
我们什么时候想见面都行，我明白了
Here are your contacts
这是您的联系人
I'ma talk about the development of
我要谈谈……的发展。
she has club system the tree
她有俱乐部系统那棵树
Our cloud platform
我们的云平台
is at the core of our pursuit
是我们追打的核心
to provide the ultimate user experience
提供终极用户体验
in the first quarter
在第一季度
continue to invest our energy resources
继续投资我们的能源资源
in the construction of infrastructure
在基础设施建设中
for our cloud platform to ensure that we can
对于我们的云平台，以确保我们可以
maintain efficient product aeration
保持有效的产品曝气
in the iot industry
在物联网行业
Meanwhile, we have proposed
同时，我们已经提议
a number of innovative industry solutions
多个创新的行业解决方案
Provide can realities for customers
为客户提供CAN现实
to quickly enter the market
快速进入市场
You barely know union a TT do moment
你几乎不知道工会是怎么回事
A christian and long
一个基督徒，一个长期的
I mean, time him somewhat a young person
我是说，把他当做年轻人
and submit an unconscious
然后提交一份无意识的
For example, in the first photo of 2021
例如，在2021年的第一张照片中
we launched energy-saving sell products
我们推出了节能促销产品。
by analyzing and predicting
通过分析和预测
the energy consumption data of users
用户能耗数据
Spot devices
现场设备
we are able to provide customers with
我们能够为客户提供
energy consumption monitoring
能耗监测
alert when energy management
能源管理时发出警报
operation and maintenance
运维
and power our customers of prospect
并为我们潜在的客户提供动力
consumer, commercial and industrial sectors
消费、商业和工业部门
by enabling them to
通过使他们能够
quickly build a complete set of energy
快速构建一套完整的能源
applications, products, systems
应用程序、产品、系统
This is home to the woman mentioned
这里就是刚才提到的那个女人的家
ching hai ya
清海亚
Soon as you decide
一旦你决定
you and companion woman for the iso/iec
你和国际标准化组织/国际电工委员会的女伴
to the dance concert again in kuopio
再次参加库奥皮奥的舞蹈演唱会
29th and buddha say time in ancient incision
29和佛陀在古代切口中说时间
disinter 2007, change your stalker
挖掘2007，更换你的跟踪者
Time to go to the super nintendo
是时候去超级任天堂了
I'll kill you
我要杀了你
I hope they keep album
我希望他们能保留专辑
Did y'all happen again
你们又重蹈覆辙了吗？
Find you to the ante
找到你的赌注
Need to constantly do something
需要不断地做一些事情
It's an annoying in science and
这在科学界是个烦人的问题
sometimes
有时候
Moreover, we provide a health care service
此外，我们还提供医疗保健服务。
cloud product system
云产品体系
for smart device manufacturers
对于智能设备制造商
in the healthcare industry
在医疗保健行业
In terms of cloud security
在云安全方面
we have obtained for certifications
我们已经获得了认证
including the cloud security alliance
包括云安全联盟
star certification
星级认证
issued by the british standards institution
由英国标准机构发布
and organization
和组织
instrumental to the formation of the iso
有助于国际标准化组织的形成
and IEC
和IEC
Syria is the world's first iot
叙利亚是世界上第一个物联网
cloud platform to hold these
云平台可容纳这些
for certifications
有关认证的信息
At the same time
在同一时间
we also successfully complete the service
我们也成功地完成了这项服务
organization control to type 2 certification
对类型2认证的组织控制
performed by eny in the first quarter
由eny在第一季度完成
Our RD , capabilities and data security
我们的研发、能力和数据安全
have always been essential to our growth
一直对我们的成长至关重要
strategies
策略
As of march 31st, 2021 are
截至2021年3月31日，
number of employees
员工人数
has increased to almost 2900
已经增加到将近2900个
from 2258 at the end of 2020
从2020年底的2258
70%of which are indeed had cancer
其中70%确实患有癌症
This allows us to lay the foundation for our
这使我们能够为我们的
sustainable development going forward
展望未来的可持续发展
It's absolutely, if you do this on here
绝对是，如果你在这里做这个
that concludes my prepared remarks
这就是我准备好的讲稿
for the first quarter
第一季度
Now I'll turn the call over to jesse
现在我把电话转给杰西
our CFO, to review the financial details
我们的首席财务官，检查财务细节
Thank you all for joining us
感谢大家收看我们的节目
Let me start by reviewing our financial results
让我首先回顾一下我们的财务业绩。
for the first quarter of 2021
2021年第一季度
and then I will discuss our outlooks
然后我会讨论我们的观点
for the second quarter
第二季度的
Before I begin
在我开始之前
please note that all amounts are in us dollars
请注意，所有金额都是美元。
and all comparisons are young year basis
所有的比较都是以年轻的年份为基础的
unless otherwise stated
除非另有说明，否则
First of all, like to highlight that
首先，我想强调的是，
our total revenue for the first quarter
我们第一季度的总收入
has bitten straight
已经被咬直了
consensus estimates by approximately 14%
共识估计约为14%
which it robots
这是它的机器人
operational and financial growth
运营和财务增长
In the first quarter
在第一季度
our total revenue will two hundred percent
我们的总收入将达到百分之两百
to fifty six point nine million dollar
五千六百九十万美元
Such strong growth
如此强劲的增长
was mainly driven by the solid growth of our
主要是由我们的稳健增长推动的
iot pass revenue, which increased
物联网通行证收入，增加了
two hundred twenty seven percent
227%
to forty nine point nine million dollars
到4990万美元
Several categories of our iot passed out
我们的物联网有几个类别已经失效
the products achieved notable
产品取得了令人瞩目的成绩。
year-over-year growth
同比增长
in particular our revenue of iot past
尤其是我们过去物联网的收入
empowering security
增强安全性
and the sensor product rule
和传感器产品规则
more than 300%ain't
超过300%的人没有
Our revenue of iot past
我们过去物联网的收入
empowering sports and wellness products
增强运动和健康产品的能力
will approximately seven hundred percent
会有大约百分之七百的人
and our revenue of iot pass
我们的物联网通行证收入
empowering education, entertainment
增强教育、娱乐能力
and network portal products
和网络门户产品
grow more than 20 volts
增加到20伏以上
I also like to remind everyone that every year
我还想提醒大家，每年
there are seasonal fluctuation
有季节性的波动。
in our revenues and cells
在我们的收入和细胞中
Typically, we experienced lower revenues
通常情况下，我们的收入较低
in the first quarter
在第一季度
while the fourth quarter is
而第四季度是
historically our strongest quarter of the year
从历史上看，我们一年中表现最好的一个季度
This is still
这仍然是
to the operation patterns of our customers
针对我们客户的运营模式
global consumer electronics brands and OEM
全球消费电子品牌和OEM
Besides past, our revenue from stars and others
除了过去，我们从明星和其他人那里获得的收入
increased by 200, 24%, 233
增加了200，24%，233
23 million dollar
2300万美元
Our brand agnostic starts
我们的品牌不可知论开始了
offerings continue to attract customers
产品继续吸引客户
interested in increasing their efficiency
对提高他们的效率感兴趣
and productivity in managing their business
以及管理业务的工作效率
and a smart device
和一个智能设备
product or customer account for the segment
细分市场的产品或客户帐户
has increased by about a hundred
已经增加了大约一百
eighty-three percent
83%
Meanwhile, our non-core business
同时，我们的非核心业务
smart distribution, revenue, grew by 30%
智能分销、收入增长30%
eight percent
8%
to four point eight million dollar
到480万美元
driven by increases in customer purchases
受客户购买量增加的推动
and demands
和要求
Our gross profit increased by 300
我们的毛利增加了300
and 74 percent
74%的人
to twenty three point four million dollars
二千三百四十万美元
while gross margin improved to 411%
毛利率提高到411%
from 303%
从303%
Our teapot gross margin increased to
我们的茶壶毛利增加到
417%from 305 percent a year ago
417%，一年前为305%
primarily due to three reasons
主要是因为三个原因
first hour increase, economies of scale, l ii
第一小时加薪，规模经济，l ii
O, improved efficiency for iot
o，提高物联网效率
past employment
过去的工作经历
achieved through effective item d
通过生效项目d实现
and the third expansion into higher margin iot
第三次向利润率更高的物联网扩张
past product lines
过去的产品线
Our out he passed gross margin has improved
我们的毛利率已经提高了。
for nine consecutive quarters
连续九个季度
Our premier iot past customers were
我们首屈一指的物联网过去的客户
216 for the trailing 12 months
过去12个月216元
ended march 31st, 2021
截止到2021年3月31日
up 73%from$125
从125美元上涨73%
for the same period ended spooky 420
在同一时期以幽灵420结束
during the first quarter of 2021
在2021年第一季度
they accounted for approximately
他们大约占到了
86%of iot pass
86%的物联网通行证
Revenue
收入
Dollar based on that
以此为基础的美元
expansion rate for our iot path segments
我们物联网路径细分市场的扩展率
improved
改进
to 210 percent for the trailing 12 months
到过去12个月的210%
ended march 31st, 2021
截止到2021年3月31日
from a hundred seventy three percent
从173%
for the same period ended march 31st, 2020
截至2020年3月31日的同期
The improvement reflects our
这一改进反映了我们的
our strong ability to
我们有很强的能力
expand our platform usage over time
随着时间的推移，扩大我们的平台使用量
and the grow revenues from existing customers
以及来自现有客户不断增长的收入
Our dollar, based on net expansion rate
美元，按净扩张率计算
has been higher than a hundred
已经超过了一百
sixty percent for six consecutive quarters
连续六个季度为60%
since we began tracking it
自从我们开始追踪它
for the trailing 12 month period
往绩12个月期间
And it's december 31st, 2019
今天是2019年12月31日
Now, turning to our operating expenses
现在，谈到我们的运营费用
please note that we excluding sure
请注意，我们不包括保险。
based compensation for our non-gaap numbers
基于非GAAP数字的薪酬
to provide a greater clarity on the chance of our
为了更清楚地了解我们的
Operating base expenses
运营基础费用
so that you can review performance
以便您可以检查性能
in the same way as our management
就像我们的管理层一样
During the quarter, non-gaap
在本季度，非GAAP
and expenses increased by a hundred percent
费用增加了百分之百
to thirty point nine million dollar
到三千九百九十万美元
primarily as a result of increased iron d
主要是由于铁含量增加所致
personnel
人员
As of march 31st, 2021
截至2021年3月31日
the company had about 2000, 80 research
该公司有大约2000，80项研究
and the development employs
并在开发中采用了
approximately 93 percent year over year
同比约93%
As a percentage of total revenue
占总收入的百分比
non-gaap and expenses decrease to 54%
非GAAP和费用降至54%
from 81 percent a year ago
一年前为81%
Continued investment in RD , talent
继续投资研发，人才
is critical for our growth strategy
对我们的增长战略至关重要
and allow us to expand our product coverage
并使我们能够扩大我们的产品覆盖范围
enhance our service offerings
增强我们的服务产品
and widen our lead in iot industry
并扩大我们在物联网行业的领先地位
Now, upstairs in the maxime
现在，在楼上的马克西姆
spence has increased by 74%
斯宾塞增长了74%
to fourteen point three million dollar
到1430万美元
mainly due to increase in employee related
主要原因是与员工相关的员工数量增加
quartz and marketing spending
石英和营销支出
The marketing spending includes
营销支出包括
costs related to hold events like the trulia
与举办Trulia等活动相关的费用
iot online expo and expo that connects brands
物联网在线博览会和连接品牌的博览会
oems and other developers
OEM和其他开发商
to explore business opportunities
发掘商机
within the tree are performing ecosystem
在树内执行生态系统
It also includes cost for developer conference
它还包括开发者会议的费用
led by to your
由引导至您的
Each developer conference
每次开发者大会
attracts thousands of developers
吸引了数以千计的开发者
from different backgrounds
来自不同的背景
to share their views on the latest iot
分享他们对最新物联网的看法
chance and development practices
机遇与发展实践
As a percentage of total revenues, non-gaap
占总收入的百分比，非GAAP
sales and marketing expenses decrease
销售和营销费用减少
to 25%from 43 percent a year ago
从一年前的43%提高到25%
Now gap see innate sense
现在差距看到了与生俱来的感觉
has increased by a hundred twenty four percent
增加了百分之一百二十四
to five point three million dollar
到530万美元
mostly due to team extension
主要是由于团队扩展
IPO related expenses
IPO相关费用
and increase the public company car
并增加上市公司的车辆
We have hired and will continue to hire
我们已经并将继续招聘
more professional and experiences employees
更专业、更有经验的员工
to further improve our internal management
进一步完善我们的内部管理
As a percentage of revenue
作为收入的百分比
non-gaap DNA expenses decrease 293%
非GAAP DNA费用下降293%
from 124 percent a year ago
一年前为124%
In the first quarter hour
在第一刻钟内
Now get lost from operation
现在从行动中消失吧
was twenty four point five million dollar wire
是价值二千四百五十万美元的电汇
Our non-gaap net loss was
我们的非公认会计准则净亏损是
twenty three point two
23.2
Twenty three point eight million dollar
2380万美元
Our non-gaap operating margin
我们的非GAAP营业利润率
was negative 43 percent
负43%
narrowing six two percentage points
收窄6个2个百分点
And from negative 105 percent in the center
从中心的负105%
it up 2020, and I'm not getting
它上升到2020年，我不会得到
that margin was negative 418%, narrowing
这一利润率为负418%，正在收窄
576 percentage points from negative
从负值下降576个百分点
994%in the centuries of 2020
在2020年的几个世纪里，99.4%的人
The narrowing of operating on the net margin
净利润率的收窄
is mainly due to
主要是因为
the increase in our operating leverage
我们经营杠杆的增加
as we achieved very strong growth
因为我们实现了非常强劲的增长
while maintaining healthy margins
同时保持良好的利润率
Net cash using operating activities
使用经营活动的现金净额
for the first quarter of 2021 was
2021年第一季度的
thirty two point seven million dollar
三千二百七十万美元
or 574%of revenue
或收入的574%
compared to 31 million dollar
相比之下，3100万美元
or a hundred sixty three point
或一百六十三分
eight million dollars, percentage of our revenue
800万美元，占我们收入的百分比
in the first quarter of 2020
2020年第一季度
The decrease in net cash
净现金的减少
using operating activities
使用运营活动
as a percentage of revenue
作为收入的百分比
was due to our rapid business growth
是因为我们的业务快速增长
and continued improvement
并持续改进
in operating efficiencies
在运营效率方面
Moving on to the back, see it
移到后面，看看它
as of march 31st, 2021
截至2021年3月31日
our cash cash equivalents
我们的现金现金等价物
and short-term investments increase, too
而且短期投资也在增加。
one point to two billion dollar
1分到20亿美元
from a hundred seventy
从一百七十开始
nine hundred million dollar
9亿美元
as of december 31st, 2020
截至2020年12月31日
primarily due to the net proceeds
主要是由于净收益
obtained from our successful missing
从我们的成功失踪中获得的
We believe this balance
我们相信这个平衡
is insufficient to meet our current liquidity
不足以满足我们目前的流动资金
and the working capital needs
以及营运资金需求
to support our strong growth
以支持我们强劲的增长
Now, turning to outlooks for the assistant
现在，让我们来看看这位助理的看法。
for the second quarter of 2021
2021年第二季度
we expect total revenues to be in the range of
我们预计总收入将在
78 million dollar, 281 million dollar
7800万美元，2.81亿美元
which has been raised by approximately
它已经提高了大约
19%to 23 percent
19%至23%
compared with street consensus estimates
与街头巷尾的普遍估计相比
This forecast reflect our current
这个预报反映了我们目前的情况
and preliminary views on the market
以及对市场的初步看法
and our operating conditions
以及我们的运营条件
which are subject to change
它们可能会发生变化
This concludes our prepared remarks for today
我们今天的准备发言到此结束。
Operator, we are now ready to take questions
接线员，我们现在准备接受提问
Thank you, thank you to ask a question
谢谢，谢谢您的提问
You'll need to press
你需要按下
star one on your telephone and together
在你的电话上打一颗星，然后一起
a question
一个问题
Press the pound key as a reminder
按拍击键作为提醒
when asking the question
在提出问题时
Please state your question in chinese first
请先用中文陈述你的问题。
then immediately put your question in english
然后立即用英语提问。
for the convenience of everyone
为了方便大家
in the call they found by
在他们发现的电话中
will be compelled to any losses
将被迫承担任何损失
Your first question comes from
您的第一个问题来自
the line of cailleach on which the ICC
国际刑事法院在Cailleach线上
your line is open
您的线路已开通
She's our 1410 cut
她是我们的1410分成
So sample sequence to show that you're here
所以样本序列显示你在这里
and your education
你所受的教育
The routine, um, email from esophageal
例行公事，嗯，从食道发来的电子邮件
Quote our choo choo shimmy
引用我们的Cho Choo Shimmy
Only a cheap deal and there are going to be in
只有一笔便宜的交易，那里就会有
as you're going
当你走的时候
You won't look, too anybody inaudible
你不会看的，任何人都听不见
Now we can evaluate the army
现在我们可以评估军队了
that whole tray of chicken
那整盘鸡肉
about the solution so we know, like the
有关解决方案的信息，这样我们就知道了，比如
the piece of glass from the mcholland stuff
麦克霍兰德事件中的那块玻璃
isn't extension point for this year
不是今年的延长点吗
the second one
第二个是
about regarding to D-Day, RD , investment
关于诺曼底登陆日、研发、投资
So what we are focusing on this year
所以我们今年的重点是
on the pr and actually have a book
在公关上，实际上有一本书
can cause a different segment in crew
可能会在船员中造成不同的分段
like stars attacks
就像群星袭击一样
the server returning to the field house
服务器返回到野外办公场所
acquired affiliate group
被收购的分支组
domestic appliance business
家电业务
So what's the synergy between wean
那么断奶和断奶之间的协同作用是什么呢？
the philips and the trulia
飞利浦和特鲁里亚
regarding trudy pillow health
关于特鲁迪枕头的健康
Feel healthy investment in future
感受未来的健康投资
Thank you
谢谢
Okay, so first let me take the first question
好的，首先让我回答第一个问题
about nine industry solutions
关于九个行业解决方案
So two years has been
所以两年已经过去了
always developing a open and neutral platform
始终开发开放中立的平台
for all their industry developers
对于他们所有的行业开发人员
And we encourage developers
我们鼓励开发商
modern the home electronics
现代家用电器
to join the platform to help grow the business
加入该平台，帮助业务发展
I would say business beyond the consumer
我想说的是，商业超越了消费者
electronics, like commercial electronics
电子学，就像商业电子学一样
commercial
商业广告
I would say business industry
我会说商业行业
agriculture, energy, health, entertainment
农业、能源、卫生、娱乐
So that's why this year
所以这就是为什么今年
we published the 9-3 solution
我们发布了9-3解决方案
to all the developers
致所有开发者
and we will continue, unless I'm the, to
我们会继续，除非我是，
provide better solutions for broader industries
为更广泛的行业提供更好的解决方案
And then it's young ourselves
然后它自己也很年轻
All the facts
所有的事实
we are still focused on the for business
我们仍然专注于业务
jerry has mentioned
杰瑞提到过
That's real estate and the camera
那是房地产和摄像机
and the community hotel and apartment
还有社区酒店和公寓
commercial lighting and the consumer security
商业照明与消费者安全
So for the staff business, we expect
因此，对于员工业务，我们预计
it will also benefit from the 9-3 solutions
它还将受益于9-3解决方案
And the way you still expect
以及你仍然期待的方式
our substances will have a very strong growth
我们的物质将会有非常强劲的增长
Continued the q1 momentum
延续第一季度的势头
and the for the long-term future
而对于长远的未来
Wind guardian
风之卫士
you go
你去吧
This would have hunting
这将会有狩猎
You can't
你不能
I'm interning at home
我在家里实习
consoles to return journey between the me
游戏机将在我之间返回旅程
So a woman taking anything but again
所以一个女人除了再吃一次外，什么都不吃
planet felucia
费卢西亚行星
to the way wasn't I in canada
顺便说一句，我不是在加拿大吗？
At the end, he goes to crying woman, that thing
最后，他去找哭泣的女人，那个东西
A girl cry, talking honey, you gotta lose
女孩哭了，说话了，亲爱的，你必须输
That you do to a woman who came funda
你对一个来芬达的女人所做的事
Then you could cope with a indian times
那你就可以应付印第安人时代了
in a game park
在游乐场里
It is what I act out to the hypogeum
这就是我对地下世界的所作所为
You can see that you can have a woman
你可以看到你可以拥有一个女人
the audi company thing
奥迪公司的事
which is what company you can in the future
哪一家公司是你未来能做的？
and get some time
争取一些时间
I cancel it
我取消了它
So interesting that you can
太有趣了，你可以
You go find game
你去找游戏吧
and you just hope she doesn't kill the man
你只希望她不会杀了那个人
who rises to particular
谁会变得特别
You got
你得到了
You better send data to sit through
你最好把数据发过去
A woman in your weight wasn't called
像你这么重的女人不会被叫来
Would total that thing of white in there you go
会把里面的白色东西加起来吗？
In fact, considering the podium
事实上，考虑到领奖台
obviously the chairwoman partisan
显然这位女主席是游击队成员
a girl, a woman
一个女孩，一个女人
If I die, somehow you-leave it in the office
如果我死了，不知何故你-把它留在办公室
Kaiser
凯撒
love each one
爱每一个人
Containment a paragraph
包含一段文字
You can do group activities
你可以做小组活动
that you could accompany the young fans
你可以陪着年轻的歌迷
So it is a woman who changing
所以是一个女人在改变
And we got to understand reality
我们要了解现实
So let me take the second question
所以让我回答第二个问题
in terms of the RD , investment is planning for this year
在研发方面，今年的投资正在计划中。
we are going to focus on several things
我们将把重点放在几件事上
But before that, let me just reiterate
但在此之前，让我再重申一遍
importance of rd for our company
研发对我们公司的重要性
Please, since the inception of our company
拜托，自从我们公司成立以来
we've always
我们一直以来
prioritize the development of technology
优先发展技术
because it is in our DNA to innovating
因为创新是我们的基因
the technology
这项技术
and our company is a ird inventory
我们公司是一家税务局库存公司。
develop different company
发展不同的公司
and that is why they are able to construct
这就是为什么他们能够建造
a high entry barrier or a competitive modes
高入口屏障或好胜模式
In the past seven years, that is because
在过去的七年里，那是因为
we have been deeply rooted in technology
我们深深扎根于技术
and our d, and so going forward
和我们的d，所以往前看
we will continue to spent locked in
我们将继续被锁在
our investment in technology and product
我们在技术和产品上的投资
invitation
邀请函
Now for this year
现在是今年的情况
we are going to invest in three main aspects
我们将在三个主要方面进行投资
The first is our developer, rd platform
第一个是我们的开发者，研发平台
which will
它将会
in it continue to enable drd of hardware
其中继续启用硬件DRD
and support the iot apps development
并支持物联网应用程序开发
and auntie cloud platform
和大妈云台
cloud platform development
云平台开发
The second investment will continue
第二笔投资将继续进行。
will be in the business expansion
将在业务扩展中
especially in the auditorium
尤其是在礼堂里
ability scenario now
现在的能力方案
In the past and as a result of the pandemic
在过去和作为大流行的结果
we will mainly focusing on
我们主要关注的是
will mainly focused on smart home scenario, and
将主要关注智能家居场景，以及
it has allow us to actually grown up business
它让我们能够真正成长为企业
in a very solid ground
在非常坚实的基础上
However, in the post pandemic, arab
然而，在大流行后，阿拉伯
people are beginning to actually go outdoors
人们开始真正走出家门
and people are beginning beginning to travel
人们开始出行
and so strong demand for this month
所以这个月的需求很旺盛
So that is why at
所以这就是为什么
we are building a new office
我们正在建造一间新办公室
with a team of 500 people
拥有一支500人的团队
in shanghai this year
今年在上海
that are going to focus on this expansion
他们将把重点放在这个扩张上
and we are going to invest in a lot of RD
我们将在研发方面投入大量资金
that can empower this kind of business
能够为这类业务提供动力的
expansion
扩展
And the cert
以及证书
areas of investment will be in actually
投资的领域实际上将在
what we call the ultimate user experience
我们所说的终极用户体验
for the final users
对于最终用户
And we call it actually
我们实际上叫它
the sixth plus end experience
六加结束体验
So is it basically this about solving richard
所以基本上就是为了解决理查德
amount of the market
市场成交量
in terms of all of the needs that we observe
就我们观察到的所有需求而言
from the market, including energy saving is
从市场上看，包括节能在内的
patient's imprisonment
监禁病人
and achievement of sadness, etc
以及悲伤的成就等
Etc, what
等等，什么？
we are solving these 6 plus and amount
我们正在解决这6个加数和金额
and we hope that through this investments
我们希望通过这项投资，
we are able to continue
我们可以继续
to drive the profitability of our company
来提高我们公司的盈利能力
and also expand our business
同时也扩大了我们的业务
Thank you
谢谢
So for the third question
那么第三个问题呢？
hill house was our primary shareholder
希尔豪斯是我们的主要股东
prior to going public
在上市之前
and one of our cornerstone
我们的基石之一
I hear, investor
我听说了，投资人
they have been very supportive of to y'all
他们一直非常支持你们
and have introduced many customers
并介绍了许多客户
in their portfolio to us
在他们给我们的投资组合中
And
和
we also helped her house portfolio companies
我们还帮她安排了投资组合公司的房子
to accelerate their business intelligence
加速他们的商业智能
and generate greater value through iot
并通过物联网创造更大价值
So philippines was already our customer
所以菲律宾已经是我们的客户了
before, and he indeed did
以前，他确实做到了
introduce a broader team of phillips to us
向我们介绍一个更广泛的菲利普斯团队
And we believe the cooperation with phillips
我们相信与菲利普斯的合作
will accelerate through the help of her house
会在她房子的帮助下加速
and we should be able to support philip
我们应该能够支持菲利普
to develop a wider range of iot products
开发更广泛的物联网产品
in the future
在未来
Positive cheering to see
积极欢呼看
all right
好的
Your next question comes from the line of
您的下一个问题来自于
young you with morgan stanley
与摩根士丹利一起年轻的你
Your line is open, she said
“你的线路已经开通了，”她说
What are you doing on sunday
你星期天打算做什么？
21st century john wayne
21世纪约翰·韦恩
Make sense
讲得通
Addition, when josh and jake-
另外，当乔什和杰克-
ee xavier rodriguez issue just eagle and t
Ee Xavier Rodriguez问题只是老鹰和t
there are going teacher shall win
有人去了，老师会赢的
charge a coyote pasta cooking job
向土狼意大利面的烹饪工作收费
Tell you which issue am called
告诉你我叫哪个问题
little canola oil
少量菜籽油
Shine with a simpie and to ensure quality
以简单的方式闪耀，并保证质量
Geology on illegal hunting, jamia
关于非法狩猎的地质学，贾米亚
we like to think they are g to show the dream
我们喜欢认为他们是在展示梦想
This angle
这个角度
when teacher zhang wen in charge of you
当张文老师负责您的工作时
sugar coating each
每个都涂上一层糖
she told me that I would be teaching
她告诉我我要去教书
language acquisition
语言习得
teaching that you go ashore
教导你上岸
Surgical considerations
外科手术注意事项
I'll translate the question briefly
我将把这个问题简略地翻译一下。
the first one of good management
良好管理的第一条
to share about the rough fleet of all
分享关于所有粗暴舰队的信息
for revenue or volume
收入或销量
among different categories
在不同的类别之间
lightning or electrical
闪电或电气
wearables and home appliances, etc
可穿戴设备和家用电器等
And what is mix, all to look in future
什么是混合，都是为了未来的展望
The second question is iot
第二个问题是物联网
past pricing strategy
过去的定价策略
especially in an environment of ships
尤其是在有船的环境中
a shortage or rising price
短缺或价格上涨
especially after, especially given the to kill
尤其是在此之后，尤其是考虑到
very strong revenue guidance
非常强大的收入指引
What should be the gross margin
毛利率应该是多少？
outlook for the second quarter
第二季展望
The third question felt
感觉到的第三个问题
could management share about the investment
管理层可以分担这笔投资吗？
focus of strategy of the newly established
新成立企业的战略重点
the iot investment fund
物联网投资基金
together with hugh half
和休·哈夫一起
Thank you
谢谢
Okay, thank you, young
好的，谢谢你，杨
So let me take the or three questions
所以让我回答一两个问题
So first
所以首先
So in the past seven years to your has been
所以在过去的七年里你一直
helping the developers and global customers
帮助开发商和全球客户
to quickly expand their products
快速扩展他们的产品
As a lot of all of our investors know
正如我们许多投资者所知道的那样
back to when we started, back to 2015
回到我们开始的时候，回到2015年
2016年
We started from
我们从
lighting and electrical segment of product
产品的照明和电气部分
and however
然而，
we have expanded it into other product lines
我们已将其扩展到其他产品线。
very quickly
非常快
As jerry also mentioned in q1 legal
正如Jerry在Q1 Legal中也提到的
expanding to more very interesting
扩展到更有趣的
high demand iot products
高需求物联网产品
to support those new it products
来支持那些新的it产品
So back to 2018, for example
所以回到2018年，举个例子
the iot path revenue contribution
物联网路径收入贡献
from lighting and the electrical segment
从照明和电气部分
were close to 90%
接近90%
But today, for example, in q1
但今天，例如，在第一季度
2020, the revenue contribution
2020年，收入贡献
from lighting and electrical
从照明和电气
is now less than 60%
现在还不到60%
Be home appliance, including large appliance
家用电器，包括大型家电
more times and the kitchen appliance a
次数越多，厨房用具就越多
contribute more than 10%
贡献超过10%
of our teapot revenue
我们茶壶收入的一半
The security and sensor segments
安全和传感器部分
on the LT package revenue come to bills
关于LT套餐的收入计入账单
also more than 10%
也超过10%
The remaining, which were quite fragmented
剩下的，相当零散的
including, for example, the health and sports
例如，包括健康和体育
the education gateways, agriculture, energy
教育门户、农业、能源
all those
所有这些
a lot of new segments of the iot products
物联网产品的许多新细分市场
I would be passed in power
我就会成为掌权者
They also contribute more than 10%
他们的贡献率也超过10%。
So we believe in the long term future
所以我们相信长远的未来
we will be more diversified
我们将更加多元化
We like to make the iot platform
我们希望将物联网平台
a very flexible or
一个非常灵活的或
to support all the iot devices that customers
支持客户的所有物联网设备
including the individual customers
包括个人客户
and the corporate customers
以及企业客户
Strong demand for
对……的需求旺盛
Second question about the pricing
关于定价的第二个问题
so what happened in the the trip industry
那么旅游行业发生了什么呢？
The see it in terms of the pricing
他们从定价的角度来看这件事。
and the shortage
以及短缺
has been once of time in the last 30 years
在过去的30年里有一次
so it is a tough time for the entire industry
因此，对于整个行业来说，这是一段艰难的时期
for all
为了所有人
the downstream industry has been impacted
下游产业受到冲击
So we have been working very closely
所以我们一直在密切合作
and carefully with our partners
仔细对待我们的合作伙伴
including our supplier partners
包括我们的供应商合作伙伴
and our customers
和我们的客户
So in terms of pricing, we will pass the the
所以在定价方面，我们会通过
the increase from the chips to the downstream
从芯片到下游的增长
But at the new wire
但是在新的电线上
to work hard in terms of the iron d, in terms
在铁d方面努力工作，在铁d方面努力工作。
Operation efficiency to help
有助于提高运营效率
to drop the cost as much as possible
尽可能降低成本
to help our customers
帮助我们的客户
to maintain a reasonable price
保持合理的价格
for the end users
对于最终用户而言
So we expect our margin will remain stable
因此，我们预计我们的利润率将保持稳定。
in the, in, the, in the next quarter
在，在下一个季度
and and also in terms of the supply
而且在供应方面也是如此
We will work very closely
我们将密切合作
continuously in the morning to your situation
早上不断地根据你的情况
to ensure that our squirrels can be supported
以确保我们的松鼠能够得到支持
The the last question is about the body defense
最后一个问题是关于身体防御的。
So we expect in q2
因此我们预计在第二季度
we will finish the setup of the iot foundation
我们将完成物联网基础的设置
Also building up the team just out, he found
他还发现，刚刚建立起来的团队
The purpose of the iot function is
物联网功能的用途是
to folk songs, the both
对于民歌来说，两者都是
upstream and downstream of the iot industry
物联网行业的上下游
and also the broad developer industry
也包括广大的开发商行业
to help the entrepreneurs in this industry
帮助这个行业的企业家
to grow their business
来发展他们的业务
and also strategically grow the iot industry
并从战略上发展物联网行业
to be a bigger pine for all of us
成为我们所有人的一棵更大的松树
So we will also build up experience
所以我们也会积累经验
investment team to carefully select the project
投资团队精心挑选项目
on the the entrepreneur team
论企业家团队
with high potentials
很有潜力的
So which should help our partners
那么哪一个应该帮助我们的合作伙伴
customers, suppliers, developers
客户、供应商、开发商
and also help to yahoo grow faster
也有助于雅虎更快地成长
Thank you for all the questions
感谢您提出的所有问题
Yes, hey, thank you
是的，嘿，谢谢你
This is the end of the QA , session
问答环节到此结束。
I'd like to have the conference back
我想把会议重新开回去。
to our management for closing remarks
致我们管理层的结束语
so thank you again for joining our core
再次感谢您加入我们的核心
If you have further questions
如果您有进一步的问题
please feel free to contact us
请随时与我们联系
or requests for our IR website
或请求访问我们的IR网站
We look forward to speaking with everyone
我们期待着与大家交谈
in our next earning course
在我们的下一个赚钱课程中
Have a good day
祝你今天愉快
This concludes today's conference call
今天的电话会议到此为止
Thank you for participating
谢谢你的参与
You may now disconnect
您现在可以断开连接